The UNZAICTA website is more likely a Content Management System where the website manager can update or manage the content of each page easily using the front-end content editor. 
it was developed in 2022 by Emmanuel Kuyela, Who was the president of the association.
His contact details: emmanuelkuyelathefirst@gmaill.com
		+260976645427

Admin Side:

Login Page
*The page where the Website admin will submit their system credentials to access and manage the page content of the website.
*Home Page
*The page where the admin will be redirected after logging into the admin side of the system.
*Manage about unzaicta page
       -The page where the system admin manages the about unzaicta content of the association website.
*Executive Members
       -The page where all school courses are listed and managed.
*Milestones Page
The page where the system admin manages the milestone page content.
*System Settings
​​​​​​​     -The page where the system admin manages some other data of the website such as the association logo.

Visitor Side:

Home Page
Course Page
About Unzaicta Page 
Milestone Page

prep: Emmanuel kuyela

admin login:
username: admin
password: admin123